We talked about insurance stocks, there is
a spike coming in ICICI Lombard as well,
keep this on your radar, it
seems to be taking action, in fact, let's ask
Avni once about ICICI Lombard,
Avni, look at its chart, there is a
good move, do you see any trade,
yes absolutely, in fact, right now my
recommendation will be in this stock, in this,
ICICI Lombard has shown a good move
and a new rally has started, so
according to me,
we can buy in it only in ATM call 2220, at the current
levels, its current price is going on,
yes 2220 is going on right now,
around 58, in this we can
buy it for the target of 75-78 by placing a stop loss of 8, so it
is a very good move and it will continue
upwards,
so this is a wait for you.